What if I stop talking Grace?
That's my way of settling the bill.
Hello, I'm Grace
What did I come to settle?
For viewers who loved our drama
We have prepared an amazing ending
Even if I eat my lungs, it won't be any good
This time, I saw our CEO Hong and became a complete fan.
Everyone just gathered together.
Sorry
don't do this to me
I'm so sad
This was confirmed through numerous viewing verifications.
queen of tears
I'm going crazy
say no
Haze
Don't call my name Baek Hyun-woo
Before I know it, I see you
Even if I'm reborn a hundred times, it's all a hundred times
I want to meet you
That woman must have been incredibly pretty.
no what
I'm not saying I suck.
He just spilled something at that time.
Wipe it off
I'm going to Seoul, call me a taxi
I'm not saying Sunwoo wants a divorce.
Diamond
yes
This is the face of someone who loves the Queen of Tears
The whole world is in a daze right now
Regardless of generation or nationality
The countless viewers who loved the Queen of Tears
Another main character who completed the drama.
queen of tears
Last March 2023
Queen of Tears actors gathered in one place
Oh my, even if I’m like this
Veteran indie who has appeared in dozens of works
Oh my, I was so nervous that day.
How come everyone looks so nervous?
And finally, on the day of the first filming
Opening the first shovel to mark the beginning of the Queen of Tears
My heart was pounding, half in anticipation and half in worry.
After concentrating hard for almost a year,
I will definitely show you a fun performance.
Please look forward to it.
We ask for your interest and love.
We will continue filming diligently.
I would appreciate it if you would look forward to the Queen of Tears.
With the unison of many actors
390 days of heavy sweat
I know that's it
What Sochan ordered was a delight to the eye with its beautiful visuals.
There was also filming on location in Germany.
What is that?
Virtual studio?
They even did special filming there.
How is it? It’s really cool.
hear your voice
Going further away
A lot of people filled with thoughts about the neighborhood
Oh my, how well I took this picture.
Even while watching the broadcast.
I didn't notice a single thing.
The smiles in your eyes
More than the stories in this novel
You make me excited
I think I can get to know you
My heart doesn't stop
I'm running like I'm dying
You make me excited
Maybe it's because I worked so hard on it
After Queen of Tears aired
The response was just amazing
Do you see the Queen of Tears? Please tell me.
Me?
Hyein-ah
I'm watching it now
I haven't seen it all yet. It ended recently. It ended.
But I'm watching episode 14.
you explained it to me too
What is that?
Why why?
I heard there was something similar to kid XX.
What did you say?
Herkina
It's a department store without Herkina.
It's just a rather large restaurant.
We also have room for Herkina.
No, I don't watch dramas at all.
He keeps saying what should I do in Herkina?
That's what you were after
I need to speak up now
I watched a drama called Queen of Tears.
I'm watching it a lot right now.
Tomorrow and the day after tomorrow are the last episodes.
Actually, I'm so nervous right now
Hye-in Hong Hye-in
Ah, I do this all the time.
I cry and laugh too
I was very angry
I had a lot of fun watching it because it was so immersive.
Now, starting this week, what pleasure will I have?
What else should I live while waiting for?
Oh, and our Hyuntae and Mi-seon too.
I heard you wrote something about the Queen of Tears?
Would you like to go and meet him sometime?
you hit first
So what should I do?
Do you know what kind of shoes my shoes are?
It's broken, right?
Is boxing good too? Cool, right?
Coach, are you tired?
Oh this is okay
I think it was slightly scratched by a tree.
Hello viewers
I'm from tvN's Queen of Tears
This is Jang Yoon-ju, who plays the role of Baek Mi-seon.
Hello, I played the role of Baek Hyun-tae.
My name is Dohyun Kim. Nice to meet you.
since we filmed
I think it's been over a year since we first met.
It's been over a year
Our Queens family, our Yongduri family, our Hyunwoo Hyein
I really, really want to see you.
It's a pity that we're about to break up
But as we talk like this, I miss everyone.
When the people who used to eat at my house turn their backs and leave
You can't send it in a nice way
At least I can walk away safely.
If you don't do it, there won't be any trouble.
A guy who turns his back on me
I'm not waving my hand
It's like sheathing a knife.
It's so scary
Are you okay?
Let's have another drink.
What else should I do? You should go in. You should go home.
I think the old man adapted to Yongduri really quickly.
Have a drink with your father
When we talk and talk, I
It was a bit salty, but it made me feel at ease.
I actually called my best friend earlier.
This is my first time saying this in my life.
I don't have any money in my pocket right now
Please send me 20 million, not much.
So what?
They said it didn't work. It was ridiculous.
If your best friend did that, you might be shocked.
No, not friends.
I don't have a single 2,000 in my pocket
I feel so sorry for myself
But for in-laws and adults to accept reality,
It seemed like it would take a lot of time
There isn't anything
I don't have two thousand in my pocket
Are you lying to comfort me, in-law?
There really isn't, I've never seen it before.
The subject is famous
Father, my father, really
Baekdu Hall
honey seal
Why are you like this? Get out of the way
This building is a place where you can see your loyalty.
I'm going to use it as a medium, right?
It's not
huh?
I just really want to get my rent paid.
So Bonghae?
I'm going to say
Anyway, isn’t it our Dubong building?
What is Dubong Building?
Dugwan Bonghae's building
Oh, my God
This is so cute when viewers see it.
That's right, that's right
When I say one, two, three, I laugh and laugh.
Now one two three
Do you think that makes sense now?
Yeah, I think you're reprimanding me for doing that again.
'Cause you're a bitch to the core who only thinks about you
You don't care if the person next to you dies or not
You're just looking for a way to live
No, I mean it's a tumor.
So it seems like people always realize it only after it passes.
What Hyein said earlier
Did you know? okay?
honey
If you knew, why didn’t you tell me? Why didn’t you do it?
What have you been doing all this time?
But mom
I told you
Something big happened to me too
Don't you ask what's going on?
You're so good that you don't matter whether it's a big thing or a small thing
It's worth it.
okay
I'll take care of tomorrow
I'll do better
How much I hurt that person
And how much I loved him
from now on
Because you will have a lot of time
Slowly become kinder
okay
When you come back from surgery
us then
slowly
Let's be kind
Get out of the way
Let's see, let's see
Our second son has arrived
I was hungry
eat
Eat slowly
delicious?
According to the police
They said I got shot by some kind of gun.
yes
Because of me
Instead of me, Hyuna
I got shot
Don't cry
Our Hyunwoo
What are you not going to do with your husband?
Don't cry, don't cry
brother-in-law
Oh why?
Actually
My sister told me never to say this.
what?
It's frustrating now
ah
It's frustrating, really.
Oh, are you really crazy?
Why are you hitting me?
Come out to my husband one more time
You're really falling behind
Don't you answer?
okay
I knew
Oh sister
What about the trilogy?
This crazy guy
I saw it, brother-in-law.
a little
It's a bit brave
No this
I woke up as soon as I tore it.
Sicheol-ah
My sister has been
I was sorry
Ah, brother-in-law
I don't think my sister has come to her senses.
Go and get the professor and the adults.
But the two of us
Is this a happy ending?
Mi-seon and Hyun-tae
have a building
It feels like we're still at war
No, I
At last
Get a US ticket
Let's go to America
So did you give me that building?
you go
thank you
Even if I want to be with you, I will hold back.
I endure it because I love you
Mom kept her promise.
You endured it so well.
a young son
In that far away country
meet someone
how to live
Without even wondering
Never contacted me
You held up really well.
By the way
you
I sent my children to a strange land
I pretended not to know
I resented you
To the house where you were adopted
adoptive parents
That's how I took the money and kept it.
you abused me
Do you think I didn't know?
Those people who didn't even drink
in a drunk driving accident
Was his death an accident?
What are you talking about now?
Do you think it was an accident?
i want my son
I didn't leave it alone
or bother you
or give you a hard time
People who block your path
I didn't just sit there and watch.
It's still the same now
like that
me
here
Did you bring it with you?
I told you so
I will protect you
To do that
I do anything
Just to protect me
huh
I am you
Even if it kills me
The shares that Eunseong has accumulated so far are
How many percentages in total?
It is 15.9%
I'm going straight to the inheritance.
yes?
I just checked
my son is dead
So it's all my son's
my beggar
Yes, I understand
Mr. Moseul-i
Former Chairman Hong Man-dae
Video evidence of attempted poisoning revealed
It was shocking
After the trial, Mr.
He was immediately arrested on suspicion of attempted murder.
In addition
Investment fraud and violation of foreign exchange laws
it's okay
Mr. Hyuntae and Mr. Mi-seon
Well done to both of you
Are you saying that dramas also follow their titles?
Worthy of its name
queen of tears
No, a record of tears
In countless tears
The real thing has appeared
Also known as crybaby Baek Hyeon-woo
Are you crying?
I want to go home with you
I thought about it
Hyunwoo’s tears
Viewers cry too
I cried too
I'm sorry I didn't tell you first
We still have the lock
know
The total number of times Hyunwoo cried was
number 40
When I think about it,
rejoice average
I cried in the 2.5th episode.
I cry every day
thank you
My son is having a hard time again
why?
So cute
Use a special move
red sea
Make your heart flutter
Yes, with that
I was just born like this
What should I do?
you
To the true king of tears
appoint
wait for a sec
why?
Are you cleaning it up?
Do I need to let it go?
I get annoyed when I see it.
don't cry
There is no one like that
are you okay?
why are you crying?
I want to live too
very very
Just by looking at it
Makes viewers' hearts melt
desperate scenes
I don't remember a thing
Treating you like a stranger
What should I do if he behaves meanly?
you're mean
One or two days?
Because that doesn't matter
Just get the surgery and do well.
Just come back safely
please
and
Hyein-ah
don't do this to me
Don't make me want to keep living
I won't even recognize you
I'll be a different person
you
You promised
Even if I have a lot of debt
Even if there is more than that
I'll be by your side
therefore
do not worry
please be here too
I'm leaving
Then don't pray
I'm afraid it will come true
I'm so anxious I'm going crazy
Hyein-ah
What are you doing? This is all.
Wake
Did you have an accident?
somehow
That's right
it's crazy?
Break the glass with your bare hands
What are these hands?
what's this
Hyein-ah
I thought I was going to die
Wait a moment here
A surprise gift for viewers
As if there were only two of us in the world
As if this time will last forever
Hyunwoo and Hyein, who only loved each other
Honeymoon trip to Germany
Maybe for two people
It must have been one of the best moments of your life
Only available in the Queen of Tears Special
Honeymoon kiss scene revealed
really really
Hyein-ah
no
Don't feel pressured.
just me
It's because I like it
Just like when I came here earlier
I don't know the way
I'll go
If you don't know the way, I can go.
Youngsong Kim
Come slowly
Because I will follow you to the ends of the earth
you really
You can't understand people's speech.
Taxi came, I'll go
Go anywhere
Because I will follow you to the ends of the earth
Oh it's really going
Go anywhere
I'll follow you to the ends of the earth
Let's go somewhere
'Cause I'll chase you to the ends of the earth
Write it as the queen of tears
I read it as love
It was told in our drama
Sometimes it's sweet
Sometimes bloody moments
I just love you all the time
Then people die
queen of tears
Those moments of love
Let’s record it together
Two people whose visuals were narrative itself
I feel happy just looking at it
It looks so good
How can you be so pretty
Ms. Hong Hye-in
I feel like the whole universe these days
Just the two of us
I think it helps.
So that's what I'm saying
the whole universe
For helping us
Do you want to get married?
Please save all my memories
Because I won't do it
Just ask me to save you
you are a different person
When I'm born again
That was the first time we met
It's okay if someone comes along.
so you can be yourself
I will protect you
huh
okay
I'll believe it
No, Hong Hye-in
why are you so angry
Did you feel uncomfortable because of me earlier?
yes
A lot.
no i am
It's so cute
Baek Hyun-woo gets really drunk when he drinks.
It makes people's hearts flutter
That's Baek Hyun-woo's special move.
So where do you go
Use that special move
You shouldn't do that.
huh
I won't use it
I didn't do anything
Already caught
No, when will I see this again?
Holy box
box
I'm not an ordinary guy
Put a number tag on your uniform
Make people cry like this?
I am
Even if I'm reborn a hundred times
100 times
I want to meet you
It's love at first sight
Is it like this?
To Sucheol
Dahye was that kind of person.
hello
My name is Cheon Da-hye.
Cheon Dahye?
but
In this love
There was a tragedy planned
So your wife
Cheon Da-hye, that girl
It was a loss, right?
I am our dahye
Where do I go to find it?
I didn't take everything with me.
I left something behind
What?
me
You left me here
Go anywhere
to the end of the earth
Because I'll follow you all
you really
You don't understand how to hit someone.
Su-cheol is such an idiot.
A fool who only knows Dahye
first
There is nothing to be afraid of in the world
tiger in the wild
Sanskrit characters
She too
In front of love
It was a gentle sheep.
Oh my, Hong Beomja!
Are you crazy?
What are you doing now?
Where should I go?
Will the dragons ever go back?
Wake
Go home
You're crazy
I'm here now
Are you Kim Yu-shin?
car tires
I still have to punk
Are you not coming?
I'll bake you a madeleine.
also
Love is
Beast too
It's a way to tame it.
Do you want to see it?
That's why I
Your precious daughter
Are you going to hit me?
Negotiation is complete
Why do you want to see me?
Hey, who's the lawyer over there?
You don't know that
Dear Queen of Tears viewers,
I played the role of Vincenzo
This is actor Song Joong-ki.
Nice to meet you
Because Vincenzo has the role
I came running
Actor Kim Jae-won
I'm working hard on filming
Even if it's weak
I came to be your strength
I rather
I think I'm having more fun taking pictures.
well known to the public
3rd generation ultra-beautiful chaebol
As soon as I was born, I had a golden spoon.
A prosperous department store
Anyway, no matter what I bring
Because she’s really young
A wide variety of genres
I feel like it's mixed up
I also had a lot of fun
Also, Director Jang Young-ho
With Director Kim Yohan
Have a lot of fun on site
It feels like I'm going
You're kneeling
Evil looks evil
Do this to Jiwon again
What I felt was an incredible force
It feels like it's been a while again
I too am a viewer
as one person
queen of tears
Have fun watching it
I will cheer you on again
This was Vincenzo.
It was Vincenzo
Oh doctor
Do you provide gowns?
yes
Later then
check this
I wrote divorce.
Uselessly
hello
This is actor Oh Jong-seok.
I think you're under a lot of stress.
If you look at the person who took the sentence completion test,
What is company life like?
My boss is my wife
The boss above him
My father-in-law.
Above that, the boss
Grandfather
My in-laws on my cell phone
As soon as your name appears
My heart is racing and my hands are shaking
honey I love you
I think I'm really happy
Just thank you all
thank you
Try it
It's been a long time
I tried to sum it up
still
Do well and have fun
It was a happy time
queen of tears
Soo-Ryun Kim
Go for it
mother
I'm here
Mommy
What are you doing with your eyes?
Then try to lay it down carefully.
mother
AS is not possible
sorry
I also tried to keep my promise.
Now really
I think the time has come
mother
hello
This is actor Kim Shin-rok.
Nice to meet you
Actors I really like
It's a drama that appears a lot.
Isn’t this the most anticipated work?
Because I can appear
I was so happy
I saw a lot of happy faces again
It was so good
Thank you
will make a special appearance
Actor Lim Cheol-soo
Nice to meet you
I have a glorious heart
Will it be fun?
I do not know
It'll be fun
Go now
Please get off work.
If you don't know me, you'll keep watching.
Where
We also did our best
I'll have fun taking pictures.
Thank you
We look forward to your love
It's Hong Gil-dong's detective office.
yes yes
Gil-dong is also our family member.
I'm also an elderly person
People keep telling me
new construction
I have a lot of talent. That’s right.
Leave that building alone.
Sometimes I go out to play when I'm bored
I bought it
Stop it, you’re a detective here too.
I have a habit of disguise.
Nam Yohan, you too, come out
I have a habit of hiding.
in our office
They are friends like Woo Baekho, my brother-in-law.
Hello Hong Jin-kyung
Nam Chang-hee
Greetings to Jo Se-ho
hello
You really are a star
after that
And training like this
A lot came
It was a marathon at that time.
But now it's a detective room.
That's right
Thanks to you like this
Because we can be together again
So happy again
memories
I think I can keep it
Go for it
beyond the screen
with countless viewers
Sharing Hiro's rock
We made it together
drama king of tears
therefore
Viewers like this
The charm that captivated me
What else could there have been?
these
There is something
of our drama
Another boast
as soon as
It left a deep lingering impression
There is an epilogue.
At the bottom of our company rooftop
They say a basketball league is alive.
Oh no way
Youngsook
Come out if you can
I just
Hyein next to me like that
I wanted to live
They say this is a lifeline
why am i so short
Upset
what
Didn't you see the broadcast?
What did I just see?
I thought it was a drama
Not even my husband
Toward my ex-husband
What is desperate love?
This earnest confession of regret
never seen
stop
as you see
While you're lying down
You've become hot
It's hot
It's humiliating
why
Switch character now
They say you’re very dramatic.
She was an ambitious girl in the 1st trillion club
It's ruined overnight
She was a provisional woman who went into hiding
Now I'm a pure girl of this era
Wait a minute, President Hong Hye-in
There are also malicious comments
How long has it been since you were divorced?
this man and that man
Didn’t you do something?
Ah, without even knowing anything
Say it like this
Even dying
Isn’t it all bullshit?
this is too harsh
What is this guy’s ID?
Hey capture it
This is a pdf
Sue me right away
For your information, there is no leniency agreement.
What's wrong with your eyes?
scary
Don't let that go
Please applaud and cheer.
secretly read someone's diary
peeping
An epilogue that made me feel emotional
indeed
Another legendary epilogue
Was there
Let's watch it together
Likes
I hate it
no
Likes
I can't bear to say it directly
your sincerity
Hyunwoo conveys his message on leaves
I hate it
Likes
uh?
You like it?
Oh really?
Cuteness Limit Exceeded
Daldal numerical limit exceeded
I'm not
I am
I love you
I love you Hyein
Episode 10 was the epilogue.
Wait a minute, speed up
Please slow down
It's okay to just look at it from afar
Even if I don't try to think about it, I think about it.
Just to see your face for no reason
The road has just turned around
If this is your first time
That's just first love
The haughty girl from Queens
Hyein also had times like this.
Actually, this visual is someone's
There's no way it's not first love
At that time, Mongolian Mongolian
It brought back memories of my first love
It was the 6th epilogue.
Hello Hong Hye-in
My name is Baek Hyun-woo
I am
Hyunwoo Baek
why
I am
It's your husband
I remember everything
everything I know
let me tell you
If we don't face each other
The sincerity comes out like this.
I shouldn't cry
this
you see
This must be my first appearance
no matter what happens
you
the promise you made with me
Even if I don’t remember
I am
to be by your side
you can do it
we
Because it’s the greatest fate ever
For Hyein who lost her memory
Written with tears
Hyunwoo’s video message
love
I love you Hyein
I loved you
I will love you
Hyunwoo's affection index is the best
Episode 13 was the epilogue.
There was a time in the past when I memorized your law book.
What was the secret?
Tips for data
Because I can’t memorize everything
Just pick out what’s important
repeatedly
I was muttering
But why
just
why
Hyunwoo Baek
You can forget it
It was Hyunwoo who left a video message, but
Hyein
It wasn't okay at all
Hyunwoo Baek
Don't forget this name
A moment that might be the end of life
she used to say
three letters
Hyunwoo Baek
name
It was three characters
Hyein's affection index is the best
Episode 14 was the epilogue.
I'm so excited
laughing
crying
Just because I have this time
I was so happy
queen of tears
of my life
last romantic song
love you
Queen of tears
For coming into this world
thank you so much
For making my life happy
thank you
for two months
I'm really happy
I think it helped me survive.
queen of tears
i love you
really happy
I think I was able to pass the time
Queen of Tears Team
You worked so hard
I enjoyed the drama
Next time again
Please take care of me
thank you
tell me
I can't even convey words
wandering through time
one hazy night
you in the limit
Should I sing it and pay it?
beyond time
Recall the shining memories
We held both hands tightly
I wish
I could have told you that
I was made to love you
To love you with all my heart
hesitate alone
The words I swallowed
love
Still want you all the time
Still in a corner of my heart
Fill it with longing
wait for you
Need you all the time
Run to me like crazy
Want you
To know you're a reason
That I'm still breathing
loved
my sincerity
All the memories of being loved